<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feature
      id="com.devonfw.cobigen.eclipse.feature"
      label="CobiGen Eclipse Plug-in"
      version="5.0.0"
      provider-name="DevonFw Team">

   <description>
      The CobiGen is an incremental generator framework based on text template engines like FreeMarker or Velocity.
   </description>

   <copyright>
      Copyright © 2013-2017 Capgemini SE. All rights reserved.
   </copyright>

   <license url="https://devonfw.github.io/TermsOfUse">
      We provide the computer program of devonfw, (hereinafter &quot;Software&quot;) free of charge to download. Regarding this software the license terms of the Apache License 2.0 apply. The user shall be responsible to provide the required system environment for using the software. In accordance with the license terms of the Apache License 2.0, the user is entitled to use the Software in own / other projects (also commercial projects), provided that the copyright notice will be taken.

The software also requires open-source components of third-parties (providers), for which the respective open source license terms apply. The open-source components of third parties are not from us and must be licensed directly from the respective third party. The rights to use will be granted directly by the respective right owner to the extent of each relevant open source license terms. The user himself can download the desired third party component from the servers of the respective provider and install them in his own environment.

For a full list of the open-source components of third-parties  and applicable license terms, see https://devonfw.github.io/TermsOfUse
   </license>

   <url>
      <update label="CobiGen Eclipse Plug-in" url="https://github.com/devonfw/cobigen"/>
      <discovery label="GitHub Repository" url="https://github.com/devonfw/cobigen"/>
   </url>

   <plugin
         id="com.devonfw.cobigen.eclipse"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

</feature>
